Guide to the COYOTE Rhode Island records 1990-2019
Brown University Library
- Public Records and Related Research, 2009 - 2019; Series 5
  - Meeting notice of Rhode Island Senate Committee on Judiciary, 2019 (Box 2)
  - National Sex Worker Anti-Criminalization Principles, June 23, 2018 (Box 2)
  - News article re: teen strippers in Rhode Island, 2009 (Box 2)
  - News article re: women and violence (Box 2)
  - News article and correspondence re: Enso Spa and Body arrests, circa 2015 (Box 2)
  - Reading: Decriminalizing Indoor Prostitution: Implications for Sexual Violence and Public Health, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Search warrant and affidavit, 2014 (Box 2)
  - Syllabus by Elena Shih for "Seminar in Research Methods and Design" at Brown University (Box 2)
- Print Material, 1990 - 2019; Series 6
  - Anti-Trafficking Review: Special Issue: Sex Work, April 2019 (Box 2)
  - Assata's Testimony, 1973: zine, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Black and Pink News: newsletter, pamphlet, and sticker, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Client and Co-Conspirator: a dialogue between two sex worker advocacy activists: zine and discussion questions found inside zine (Box 2)
  - Curious Images: The Sex Worker as Subject and Artist, Poet and Politician: zine, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Ho Stage #3: zine, circa 2011 (Box 3)
  - Hustler: magazine and CD, April 2019 (Box 3)
  - International Day to End Violence Against Sex Workers: notecards, 2017 (Box 3)
  - Ladies of the Evening: The Improv 10/27/98: zine, circa 1999 (Box 3)
  - No Bad Whores Just Bad Laws Year One: zine, circa 2017 (Box 3)
  - Postcards from Prison: zine, 2011 (Box 3)
  - Prostitutes of New York Press: a newsletter published by and for the New York City sex workers' community: volume 1, number 1, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Sex on the Move: Sex Work, Migration, and Trafficking: zine (Box 3)
  - Various titles: postcards, n.d. (Box 3)
- Restricted, 2002 - 2019; Series 7
  - Bella Robinson's personal papers, 2002 - 2018; Series 7. Subseries 1
    - Applications, 2015, 2018 (Box 4)
    - Awards and certifications, 2014 - 2017 (Box 4)
    - Clipping re: Robinson's grandmother, 2002 (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, 2016 (Box 4)
    - Photos of Robinson, her daughter, and family members (Box 4)
    - Resume, circa 2017 (Box 4)
  - General Restricted Files, 2017 - 2019; Series 7. Subseries 2
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence to A. C. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence to A. M. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence to C. D. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence to C. D. B. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence to J. L. B. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence to J. P. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence to K. M. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence to L. F. W. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence to L. P. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence to L. T. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence to M. O. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence to M. S. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence to N. P. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence to R. J. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence to T. E. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with A. C. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with A. C. [original un-redacted copy], 2019 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with A. M. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with A. W. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with B. T. [original un-redacted copy], 2019 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with C. B. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with D. S. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 - 2019 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with H. K. T. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with H. K. W. [original un-redacted copy], 2019 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with J. F. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 - 2019 (Box 4)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with J. F. [original un-redacted copy], 2019 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with J. H. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with J. M. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with J. N. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 - 2019 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with K. S. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 - 2019 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with L. G. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with L. H. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with M. B. [original un-redacted copy], 2019 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with M. H. [original un-redacted copy], 2019 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with M. S. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with M. S. [original un-redacted copy], 2019 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with P. J. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with P. M. R. (1 of 2) [original un-redacted copy], 2017 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with P. M. R. (2 of 2) [original un-redacted copy], 2018 - 2019 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with R. W. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with S. B. [original un-redacted copy], 2019 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with S. D. [original un-redacted copy], 2018 - 2019 (Box 5)
    - Sex Workers Outreach Project Behind Bars: correspondence with T. W. [original un-redacted copy], 2017 - 2018 (Box 5)